[Music] Oh
[Música]
my god
madre mía
there are people who kick the chair there
hay gente que le da patadas a la Silla
are people who kick the chair Let's
hay gente que le da patadas a la Silla A
see it's time it's time it's time
ver es la hora es la hora es la hora por
where do you want to start I don't know why today
dónde quieres empezar no sé porque hoy
the
se me está como desenfocando mucho la
camera is getting so out of focus but it's because I'm not staying still
cámara pero es porque no me estoy quieto
Sure but it's hard for you not to look
Claro pero es difícil que tú no estés
good with that little face you have of a
guapo con esa carica que tienes de
handsome chorus boy that mask Piqué it
estribillano guapo esa barbija lo Piqué
But anyway a compliment But I accept it
Pero bueno un cumplido Pero te lo acepto
because it's true I'm
porque es verdad
not going to be falsely modest here
no voy a hacer aquí una falsa modestia
well godmother
bueno madrina
where do you want to start because the way
por dónde quieres empezar porque como lo
you bring it and the way this channel is yours
traes tú y como este canal Es Tuyo ya
more than mine man this channel is also
más que mío hombre este canal también es
mine it's both of ours now I mean we're even we'll
mío es de los dos ya o sea estamos a
talk How how do you want to
pachas ya hablaremos Cómo cómo quieres
do it we give first if not I think that
hacerlo damos primero si no yo creo que
to give our opinion first it's
para dar nuestra opinión primero es
better that we give the statements that we
mejor que demos las declaraciones que
have exclusively from both Olga and
tenemos en exclusiva tanto de Olga como
Marta risk not you how do you see it on a
de Marta riesgo no tú cómo lo ves a
journalistic level what do you think is
nivel periodístico qué crees que es
better
mejor
man to have all the how are we going to give our
hombre para tener toda la como vamos a
opinions the two of us well man it's not going to
opinar nosotros dos pues hombre no vaya
change In something that could
a ser que cambie En algo que pueda que
could change something in  our opinion
pueda cambiar algo en nuestra opinión
the statements that each
las declaraciones que está dando cada
of the two is giving no And they have also told me
una de las dos no Y además me han dicho
no So it is not a little word
que no O sea que no es una palabrita en
like For example what Marta has given last
plan Como por ejemplo lo que ha dado
week she has simply said I am not
Marta semana que simplemente ha dicho no
going to give her opinion but that there is an opinion there is no
voy a opinar sino que hay hay opinión no
substance there are no
hay sustancia no
substances substance dear
hay sustancias sustancia querido
very brief Marta has been very brief
muy breve Marta ha sido muy breve
could we start with Marta's What do you
podríamos empezar con lo de Marta Qué te
think has been more or we tell or
parece que ha sido más o contamos o
contextualize but I think that
contextualizamos pero yo creo que la
people here already know everything but first
gente aquí ya lo sabe todo pero primero
a context without giving an opinion in case there is
un contexto sin opinar por si hay
someone who has lived I thought that she has been
alguien que ha vivido Yo pensé que ha
closed in the closet this
estado cerrada en el armario este de
Narnia no and has not found out what has
Narnia no y no se ha enterado de lo que
happened the last hours
ha pasado las últimas horas
we tell what has happened we put what
contamos qué es lo que ha pasado ponemos
Marta does or do the others tell us
lo de Marta o sea nos cuentan los demás
is it audio or is it audio is it written no it is not
es audio o es audio es escrito no no es
written I have tried but it is written it is
escrito Yo he intentado pero es escrito
written well that remains forever now
es escrito bueno eso queda para siempre
clear it is that audio audio let's
ya claro es que audio audio
see what has happened basically It is
a ver lo que ha pasado básicamente Es
that this weekend
que este fin de semana
was Lola's birthday So
era el cumpleaños de Lola Entonces
first yes it is true that Olga
primero sí que es verdad que que Olga
uploaded a photograph to celebrate it I don't
subió una fotografía para celebrarlo no
remember if it was a story or it was a
me acuerdo si era una historia o era una
publication I think it was a post  a post
publicación creo que era un post un post
surely Didn't she upload a photo with
seguramente No subió ella una foto con
her little girl blowing out the candles I love you
su niña soplando las velas te quiero
very much and such No yes it's true that Olga
mucho y tal No sí que es verdad que Olga
always When she uploads the photo with with Lola I
siempre Cuando sube la foto con con Lola
didn't step on her which is something that I
No la pisé la que es una cosa que a mí
personally don't like and I have my
personalmente no me gusta y tengo mi
reason then when when it pleases me more I will
motivo luego cuando cuando me plalle más
explain to you but based on my experience
os explico pero en base a mi experiencia
of life okay No no because I don't like it
de la vida vale No no porque no me gusta
but not for no for you but for the people
pero no por no por ti sino por la gente
behind the internet no and then
que hay detrás de internet no y luego
when she went to the second birthday with
cuando se fue al segundo cumpleaños con
her father to celebrate it with her father Well it
su padre a celebrarlo con su padre Pues
turns out that there are a series of
resulta ser que hay una serie de
publications both on the Instagram of
publicaciones tanto en el Instagram de
Rocío Flores and Marta Riesgo like
Rocío flores como de Marta riesgo como
Antonio David in which they are commenting
Antonio David en los que van comentando
or showing us how they are experiencing the
o enseñándonos cómo están viviendo el
birthday they go to eat somewhere there is
cumpleaños van a comer a un sitio hay
a bakery there is a dinner a
una pastelería hay una cena un sitio de
hamburger place in Chueca always with the
hamburguesas de Chueca siempre con la
girl because it must be said always with
niña porque hay que decirlo siempre con
the pixelated girl the only one who doesn't
la niña pixelada la única que no la
pixelate her eh Rocío Flores her sister
pixela eh Rocío flores su hermana
too there are some tags in those
también hay unas etiquetas en esas
publications that I don't know if it's that the
publicaciones que no sé yo si es que a
places she goes to are being
los sitios a los que va les está
given birthday gifts like dinner no let's see
regalando el cumpleaños la cena no a ver
you  I can excuse me uh for interrupting you, I
yo te puedo perdón eh que te interrumpa
can assure you because I know
yo te puedo asegurar porque conozco
because even I have been
porque incluso a mí a veces me han
invited sometimes and I don't have even a
invitado también y no tengo ni la cuarta
quarter of Marta's influence nor do I
parte de repercusión de Marta ni la
want it but it
quiero pero
is 100% a gift from the pig from
es 100% un regalo de la la cerda de
Chueca 100% I mean there is a birthday
Chueca 100% O sea hay un cumpleaños
I imagine that Marta is the one who
imagino que Marta es la que lo habrá
organized it from Hey we are going to be there Antonio
organizado de Oye vamos a estar Antonio
David, it is the girl's birthday
David yo es el cumpleaños de la niña
She has organized the balloons she has
Ella ha organizado los Globos ha
organized the dinners at the time to sing
organizado las cenas en momento cantar
that is all organized and it is promotion it
eso está todo organizado y es promoción
is that that is a clear factor it could be
es que ese es un factor claro puede ser
important here because it is not the same
importante aquí porque no es lo mismo
Hey you make your own way and you go somewhere
Oye tú te buscas la vida y vas a un lado
and not because of the fact of paying money no
y no por el hecho de pagar un dinero no
but the intention I do not think is
sino la intención no creo que es
important also let's see of course it was if I'm not
importante también a ver claro era si no
mistaken it was a pastry shop
me equivoco era una pastelería
first Yes a balloon shop no or
primero Sí una una tienda de globos no o
some balloons a preparation with balloons
unos globos una preparación con globos
that they make with the number 10 I don't know what
que le hacen con el número 10 no sé qué
and then the pig from Chueca that is a
y luego la cerda de Chueca que eso es un
children's place Marina No it does not sound very
sitio infantil Marina No no suena muy
easy but it is suitable for I have been
fácil pero sí que es apto para yo estado
uh for children's themes because of like the
eh para temas infantiles por como por la
decoration  the type of dish is
decoración por el tipo de plato está
the name of the place and the neighborhood let's
el nombre del local y el barrio
see you understood me like I could
a ver me has entendido en plan podría
exactly perfectly
exactamente perfectamente
Olga yesterday spoke out on her Instagram and even though
Olga ayer se pronunció en su Instagram y
she usually doesn't speak much and she
eso que ella se suele pronunciar poco y
says due to the amount of messages
dice debido a la cantidad de mensajes
that I have received and continue to receive I'm going to
que he recibido y sigo recibiendo voy a
tell you something I absolutely do not agree
deciros algo para nada estoy de acuerdo
nor have I consented nor will I consent to the
ni he consentido ni consentiré la
excessive and unnecessary exposure that has been
exposición excesiva e innecesaria que se
made of my daughter on social media
ha hecho de mi hija en las redes
in the last 24 hours
sociales en estas últimas 24 horas
Thank you for always being there and blue heart
Gracias por estar siempre y corazón azul
and then on the other hand to complete the
y luego por otro lado para completar la
information before commenting on everything
información antes de comentarlo todo
then on the other hand Rocío Flores has also
luego por otro lado Rocío flores también
posted some stories
ha puesto unas historias
they are here in the reason but I think that
están aquí en la razón pero creo que
then there were more because here they put the
luego hubo más porque aquí ponen la
reason of your partner there was
razón de tu compañero
no Rocío Flores then she uploaded a
no hubo a Rocío flores luego subió una
story yes there were others and here wait I'm
historia sí hubo otras y aquí espérate
going to see on Twitter I'm going to see understand that surely quickly forgive me for not having it prepared no no no I think that this one look here I already have it quickly Okay, what a shame this Rocío Flores okay How sorry I am for the shitty society that we are creating and in which we still have so much
creando y en la que nos queda tantísimo
to advance absolutely ashamed of the
por avanzar absolutamente avergüenza me
amount of barbarities that  I
da la cantidad de barbaridades que
receive day after day and minute after
recibo día tras día y minuto tras
minute if you allow me I am going to enjoy
minutos si me permitís voy a disfrutar
my family which is the only thing that
de mi familia que es lo único que me
matters to me in this life the well-being of
importa en esta vida el bienestar de los
mine and my own of course I
míos y el mío propio por supuesto
will continue trying to make
Seguiré intentando hacer lo más feliz
my people as happy as I can to the person who
que pueda a mi gente a la persona que
among so much [ __ ] and lies you contribute a
entre tanta [__] y mentira aportáis un
little coherence and support towards
poquito de coherencia y apoyo hacia mi
me Thank you from the bottom of my heart and now I am
persona Gracias de todo corazón y ahora
going to get ready to go out and make some great
voy a arreglarme para salir y hacer un
plans with my brothers who are
planazo con mis hermanos los cuales son
the most important people to me in
las personas más importantes para mí en
this life with my father and his partner and with
esta vida con mi padre y su pareja y con
my partner and whoever doesn't like it I'm
mi pareja y a quien no le guste Lo
sorry but I repeat again that in
siento pero vuelvo a repetir que en la
life you have to move forward and look out for your
vida hay que avanzar y mirar por la
own happiness than
felicidad propia
ours without hurting anyone
que los nuestros sin hacer daño a nadie
and that is what I do and will continue doing
y eso es lo que hago y seguiré haciendo
all my life I cannot please everyone
toda mi vida no puedo gustarle a todo el
but neither I nor anyone deserves so much
mundo pero yo ni nadie se merece tanto
hate there is a lot to comment on here after
odio hay mucho que comentar aquí después
Marina one second Sorry to explain that yes it
Marina un segundo Perdón explicar que sí
is true that Rocío Flores uploaded this before
que es verdad que esto lo subió antes
and then it was Olga's thing
Rocío flores y después fue lo de Olga
okay Not the other way around it's that we don't know anymore
vale No al revés es que ya no sabemos ya
even with so much stuff Yes it was the other way around it was the other way
ni con tanta cosa Sí fue al revés fue al
around Sure yes yes yes yes yes it was the other way
revés Seguro sí sí sí sí sí sí fue al
around it was  the other way around, I was sure look, I
revés fue al revés segura estaba mira
was doubting it and I've read it
que lo estaba dudando y lo he leído
several times here, you see, it was long
varias veces por aquí ves fue mucho
before Olga's story, long before
antes que lo de Olga mucho antes que lo
Olga's story. Look, it's very important. I mean, there are
de Olga Mira es muy importante O sea hay
two stories,
dos historias
both stories are before Olga's.
las dos historias son antes que la de
Here, now the first thing you've read
aquí ahora lo primero que has leído
is that you've read two, I mean, when it
claro es que has leído dos o sea cuando
says How sad it is that I can't see, I almost ca
dice Qué pena me da es que no veo casi
n't see it, there's one that says How sad it is for me,
no lo veo hay uno que dice que pena me
the [ __ ] that comes from society, the
da la [__] que es de la sociedad la
[ __ ] that reaches me, I don't know what it's worth, but
[__] que me llega no sé qué vale pero
then there's another one
luego hay otra
that, to me personally, and then we'll
que a mí personalmente y luego nos
expand on that. Marina, this part here,
extenderemos Marina esta parte de aquí
if you tell me it comes before
si me dice que va antes de la historia
Olga's story, it's okay, but if you tell me it
de Olga no pasa nada pero si me dices
comes after, this part here sounds familiar to me, it
que va después esta parte de aquí me
all came before, look, I was
todo antes iba todo antes fíjate que yo
doubting, eh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, both are from
dudaba eh que sí que sí que sí que sí
before. Both are from before, so, yes, it would fit more
de antes entonces y sí que encajaría más
if it came out after, it's true that it's a
que fuera después verdad es que es una
nonsense, that and if it came out after, this would be
rayada eso y fuera después esto se
seen as a dig. Olga, of the stick,
entendería como una pulla Olga del palo
listen to me, girl, be happy with your
escúchame tía que sea feliz tú con tu
new partner and if it bothers you that my
nueva pareja y que si te molesta que mi
father and partner make plans  with us I'm
padre y pareja haga planes con nosotros
sorry but it is what it is but of course
Lo siento pero es lo que hay pero claro
if it's before no no it's none it's not a [ __ ]
si es antes no no es ninguna no es
joke Olga
ninguna [__] Olga
But what I don't know if I've reached
Pero lo que yo no sé si he llegado a
this point if it's better if we share a little bit of
este punto si mejor contamos un poco la
information or and then we give our opinions yes almost
información o y después opinamos sí casi
better than yes no What do you prefer we give our opinion
que mejor que sí no Qué prefieres
no I think it's better to tell it that
no yo creo que mejor contarlo que la
people give their opinion and then we give our opinion no
gente opine y luego opinamos nosotros no
or what but let's see Mimi is telling me that I
o qué pero a ver me está diciendo Mimi
trust Mimi a lot that
que yo confío mucho en Mimi que
all of Rocío Flores' stories
que las historias de Rocío Flores todas
or rather both are like five hours before
o sea las dos son como cinco horas antes
Olga's so here things
que la de Olga entonces aquí la cosa
change to what I
cambia a lo que yo
regarding the issue of the photos I don't
referente al tema de las fotos no
understand I understand what it
entiendo entiendo a lo que es el entre
is between them the way of carrying it because here what I saw was first a Well of course what Olga did I consider that it goes for both Marta and Rocío Flores sincerely of course I of course You read that and you think about both of them each in their own way perhaps more about Marta I think that
su manera quizá más en Marta Yo creo que
perhaps because she talks about
quizá porque habla de exposición
excessive exposure and Rocío Flores has had the same
excesiva y Rocío flores lleva la misma
line for many years I
línea desde hace muchos años yo la
know her on Instagram in the same line
conozco Instagram en la misma línea
So I think it goes a little  more out
Entonces yo creo que va un poco más por
there but let's see
ahí pero a ver
today at 1840 2000 likes not to tell
hoy en 1840 2000 likes no para contar
this Hey look I'm going to throw myself on the floor and fall
esto Oye mira me tiro al suelo y me
asleep if not You're going to like the video
duermo si no Vais a darle like al vídeo
eh I swear no no that at 2000 likes We'll
eh os juro no no que a los 2000 likes lo
count it at 2000 likes we'll count it we
Contamos a los 2000 likes lo contamos os
give you the statements that if I don't
damos las declaraciones que si no me
throw myself on the floor it's because I haven't had dinner to
tiro al suelo es que no he cenado para
be here with you and I have to go
está aquí con ustedes y tengo que irme
Then to the other three to six quickly
Luego al otro tres al seis rápido en por
in the middle if not go to give it there I'll start having dinner Okay eh Marina I'm going to throw myself here on the floor I throw myself down I take a nap and such is that let's see then we're talking Marina to give the real data no and as they are because I know that on other channels
como son porque sé que en otros canales
and in other places this has been sold
y en otros sitios se ha vendido esto
as an attack by Rocío Flores towards
como un ataque de Rocío flores hacia
Olga if we are talking then
Olga si estamos hablando que entonces
really Rocío Flores has not entered the
realmente Rocío Flores no ha entrado al
rag nor has she answered her in any
trapo ni le ha contestado de ninguna
way Olga
manera Olga
no rather it has been yes evidently
no más bien ha sido si evidentemente
those two stories are from before it is not
esas dos historias son de antes no es
an answer from Rocío something that I
una contestación de Rocío alga que yo
doubted and before the  doubt I read that And yes I think it
dudaba y ante la duda Leo eso Y sí que
is a
pienso que es una contestación en toda
full-fledged answer, which surprises me because
regla cosa que me sorprende porque
except for one occasion with Ana I
exceptuando en una ocasión que en Ana me
remember perfectly that Olga called So
acuerdo perfectamente que Olga llamó O
you that Rocío Flores
sea que tú que que Rocío flores
expressed her anger Rocío even
manifestó su enfado Rocío aunque sea
though you have oats that character has always
aunque tengas avena ese carácter siempre
publicly shown herself more or less
públicamente se ha mostrado más o menos
cautious with her father with Olga or rather
prudente con su padre con Olga o sea
even about her mother she could have said
incluso de su madre podía haber dicho
a thousand things and and except for a few occasions that
mil cosas y y exceptuando ocasiones
in the end you know what I
contadas que al final sabes lo que te
want to tell you that I would be surprised to see that
quiero decir que me sorprendería ver ese
public argument in such an
rifirrafe Público de esa manera tan
unnecessary way on the part of everyone, I mean me
innecesaria por parte de todos o sea yo
Javi one thing bothers me and it is that
Javi a mí me molesta una cosa y es que
here it seems that once again by force you have to
aquí parece que otra vez por narices te
position yourself on one side and girl
tienes que posicionar en un lado y chica
how lazy I mean you can't have an
qué pereza O sea no se puede tener una
opinion without the need for fanaticism I
opinión sin necesidad del fanatismo ese
want to tell you that I understand I understand
te quiero decir que entiendo yo entiendo
both sides in the end each one has their own thing
las dos partes al final cada uno Tiene
but it seems that exactly
lo suyo pero parece que exactamente
clear
claro
from God one or we go or it is that Or it is that we go you
de Dios una o vamos o es que O es que
are a separate picture it is a
vamos eres un cuadro aparte es un tema
hyper mega personal subject Let's see all
hiper mega personal A ver todos todos
the subjects are personal but yes it is
los temas son personales pero sí que es
true that here let's
verdad que yo aquí
see then we will is that  in the end we
a ver luego vamos a es que al final
give the opinion I understand a little I
damos la opinión Yo entiendo un poco Yo
understand both sides and there are also
entiendo las dos partes y también hay
things that I don't understand from both sides
cosas que no comprendo de ambas partes
okay But well, like I don't take a
vale Pero bueno en plan yo no me
position in this case, let's see, I can
posiciono en este caso a ver me puedo
agree more with one side than
estar más de acuerdo con una parte que
the other it's okay that's not going to be me
la otra no pasa nada eso no me va a ser
withdrawing my appreciation for Olga nor do I appreciate
retirar mi aprecio a Olga ni ni aprecio
Antonio David like or Rocío Flores
Antonio David en plan ni a Rocío flores
like I don't know I don't care they are his issues you
en plan no sé me da igual son temas suyo
understand me it's what you say that
me entiendes yo es lo que tú dices que
one thing doesn't take away from the other in the end they
una cosa no quita para la otra al final
are public figures and we can have an opinion
son personajes públicos y podemos opinar
that having an opinion
que el tener una opinión
Total that an opinion always from
Total que una opinión siempre desde el
respect and agreed criteria with a certain
respeto y concierto criterio con cierto
certain should not offend anyone because for
tal no le debe ofender a nadie porque a
me we go to come to opinions with
mí vamos que vengan a opiniones con
respect let them all come you know but but
respeto que vengan todas sabes pero pero
look if it seems to you we are
mira si te parece
going to tell
vamos a contar
what Marta is for it is very very brief but I
lo de Marta es muy muy breve pero yo
think that each one
creo que cada uno
judges no that is what they are for we are not
que juzgue no que para eso están yo no
going to judge us Marta I
vamos a juzgar a nosotros Marta le
ask him are they
pregunto son
in particular
en concreto
one of them dancing at karaoke The
una de ellas bailando en un karaoke La
girl is covered she is there are the three of them
niña está tapada está están las tres
dancing Rocío Flores Mar and Lola and the
bailando Rocío flores Marta y Lola y la
girl is covered okay And yes  It's true that
niña la tapa vale Y sí que es verdad que
the karaoke site is tagged What
está etiquetado el sitio del karaoke Que
is that? Could that also be a promotion
es que eso puede ser una promoción
Marina, let's see if you tag it for
también Marina a ver si lo etiquetas por
something? No, a promotion. No, if Marta
algo no No una promoción No si Marta
tags. Well, if Marta and anyone
etique Bueno si Marta y cualquiera
tags karaoke, it's because obviously they've either
etiqueta al karaoke es que evidentemente
invited them for drinks or
o igual les han invitado unas bebidas o
let them sing more, that's what it is, but
les han dejado cantar más eso tiene pero
Marta needs that, aunt, too.
Marta le hace falta eso tía también
Marta lives, not the same, not on this occasion,
Marta vive no igual en esta ocasión no
but Marta also lives, I mean, part of the
pero Marta vive también o sea parte del
TV thing, she has, gosh, she has
tema de la tele ella tiene jolín tiene
a lot of impact on networks and many
muchísima repercusión en redes y muchos
followers and normally every
seguidores y ya normalmente todos los
day we see it every time she tags x
días lo vemos cada vez que etiqueta a x
restaurants it's advertising. So, either they
restaurantes es publicidad O sea que o
invite her to eat or to a
le invitan a comer o a una experiencia
gastronomic experience or to a hotel. Hey, if they
gastronómica o a un hotel Oye si les
invite us because they generate it, I'm not going to
invítanos porque lo genera yo eso no lo
question that, but it's clear that
voy a cuestionar pero que está claro que
when you see them tagged on several
cuando les ves etiquetados en varias
occasions, 90% of which is bribery, what we
ocasiones al 90% que es es un cohecho
call it, you know, a gift,
que lo llamamos sabes un regalo
well, the Instagram stories, because you
pues las historias de Instagram porque
're telling me. There's one that Lola
me estáis diciendo Hay una que Lola no
isn't covered up. Not the one that Lola doesn't cover up
está tapada No la que la que no tapa
is Rocío Flores because her sister has
Lola es Rocío flores porque su hermana
never covered her. So yes.  there's
nunca la ha tapado Entonces sí que hay
one there's a story about Rocío Flores and
una hay una historia de Rocío flores y
Manuel with Lola in which she doesn't cover her
Manuel con Lola en la que no tapa la
face but that's about Rocío Flores but
cara pero eso es de Rocío flores pero
then the one that Marta uploads in particular is
luego la que sube Marta en concreto son
the three of them dancing singing Marta Rocío
las tres bailando cantando Marta Rocío
Flores and Lola but Lola covers her up and they
flores y Lola pero a Lola la tapa y
tag the place and then there's another one where she's having
etiquetan el local y luego hay otra en
dinner
la que está cenando
no no
no no
then there's another one where she was
que luego hay otra que estaba
answering a friend I
contestándole a una amiga
was answering a friend as if she were
estaba contestándolo amiga como si
here talking to her I
tuviera aquí hablando con ella
didn't get distracted then there's another
no me desconcentré luego hay otra
story where you can see Lola's
historia en la que se le ve a Lola las
hands holding the hamburger
manos cogiendo la hamburguesa
okay well the one about the birthday I don't know what
vale bien la del cumpleaños no sé qué
okay Those are the two stories I didn't
vale Esas son las dos historias no se me
miss another one
escapa otra
No I would swear I hope
No yo juraría espero que me corrija la
people here correct me I think there was a story
gente aquí creo que hubo alguna historia
that Marta deleted because of that story
que Marta borró a raíz de esa historia
about Olga it could be because I reviewed it the
de Olga puede ser porque lo repase al
next day and I didn't see it maybe
día siguiente y ya no la vi a lo mejor
I'm wrong But anyway yes I
me estoy equivocando Pero bueno si yo
think it's not about the number of
creo que no se trata ya del número de
stories It must be said other years we've
historias Hay que decir otros años
also seen that or so well that's
también hemos visto eso o sea bueno eso
good it's that here in the end it's her two
bueno es que aquí al final son sus dos
parents who decide I think and in the
padres los que deciden yo pienso y al
end we're giving our opinions like  Well you say
final estamos opinando como bien dices
that there is a lack of communication
que uno hay una falta de comunicación
between the two parents who are the ones who
entre los dos progenitores que son los
decide on Mirafon Alba
que deciden en mirafón sigue Alba
Carrillo continues a lot of fuss But they continue
Carrillo mucho jaleo Pero ellos siguen
with the child with Lucas so that he is not seen, so that
con el niño con Lucas que no se le vea
both of them are not seen I mean I think there is a
que no se le vea los dos o sea que creo
lack of communication First of all between
que hay falta de comunicación lo primero
them I think that as a result of what has
entre ellos creo que a raíz de esto que
happened and has come to light
ha pasado y ha trascendido públicamente
each one is going to take other types of measures
cada uno va a tomar otro tipo de medidas
in fact it is what you say I think that
de hecho es lo que tú dices creo que
Antonio David what he uploaded was
Antonio David lo que ha subido estaba
pixelated the girl with a Christmas tree
pixelada la niña con un árbol de navidad
or with
o con
and Olga if she considers it uploading a
y Olga si ella lo considera subir un
post with the girl blowing out a candle but the fact is
post con la niña soplando una vela pero
that she has done it they have always done it
es que lo ha hecho lo han hecho siempre
in the media we do not do it in the
en los medios no lo hacemos yo en los
media we obviously cover it up because
medios tapamos evidentemente porque
they decide but they can
ellos lo deciden pero que lo pueden
share it So if the
compartir ellos Entonces si los
parents in this case have
progenitores en este caso lo hayan
had it David decide Hey look I do not
tenido David deciden Oye pues mira no
want the girl to have that
quiero que la niña tenga esa
overexposure and such it is very clear that it
sobreexposición y tal está clarísimo que
is a zasca I see it totally towards
es un zasca yo lo veo totalmente hacia
Marta and not towards Rocío that specifically
Marta y no hacia Rocío eso en concreto
is specifically because Marta yes it is
es en concreto porque Marta sí que es
true that she uploads a lot of things  that
verdad que sube muchísimas cosas que
everyone does what they want to me it
cada uno que haga lo que quieras a mí me
gives me every time I enter I am like this
da yo cada vez que entro estoy así
seeing all of Marta's stories one
viendo todas las historias de Marta uno
another she is such a character but maybe there are
otro ella tan personaje pero que a lo
things that I understand that
mejor hay cosas que entiendo que sea
Olga bothers her
Olga le molesten
Well well what happens is that I think it
Pues bueno lo que pasa es que creo que
should have been talked about before not that they have been together for
se debería haber hablado antes no que ya
a while both Olga and her
llevan un tiempo tanto Olga como su
partner are consolidated and Marta with
pareja está consolidada y Marta con
Antonio David So it is like that I have a
Antonio David Entonces es como que me
hard time understanding at what point
cuesta entender en qué momento se ha
Olga has come to publicly come
a tener que públicamente Olga salir al
forward and say Hey I do not consent to this that
paso y decir Oye yo No consiento esto
all her rights are there too
que están todos sus derechos también
but of course also Now I understand
pero claro también Ahora entiendo que
Marta that now we are going to tell it or if
Marta que ahora lo vamos a contar o si
you like I will tell Marta's reaction to
te parece lo cuento ya la reacción de
wait
ante espera
before this because of course let's see Marta who
ante esto porque claro a ver Marta
is a tough girl
que es una tía de armas tomar
and now Marta is silent week she
y yo ahora Marta está callada semana le
told her that she was not going to say anything and
ha dicho que no iba a decir nada y a mí
if you want I will tell you
si quieres lo cuento ya
my opinion first to put it in to
mi opinión primero para meterlo
see I understand I understand both sides
a ver yo Entiendo entiendo ambas partes
okay each parent decides I am
vale cada padre decide yo estoy
totally against and I also have
totalmente en contra y además tengo
many videos on my main channel
muchos vídeos en mi canal principal
about this and explaining to people
sobre esto y explicándole a la gente
trying to make people aware that
intentando concienciar a la gente de que
not  do it but not to the level of being
no lo hagan pero no a nivel de ser
famous, I mean, not even me from here,
famoso o sea ni siquiera yo desde aquí
besides I recommend it to everyone,
además se lo recomiendo a todo el mundo
I had some really bad experiences with the
yo tenía unas experiencias muy malas en
internet with people who are
esto de internet con gente que está
crazy, there are a lot of people who
fatada la cabeza hay mucha gente que me
have told me about the report that they did on me as an
ha dicho el reportaje que me hicieron en
investigation team, imagine that or
equipo de investigación imaginaros eso o
for example what happened to me yesterday on social media,
por ejemplo lo que me pasó ayer en redes
imagine that If I were the typical
imaginaros eso Si yo fuera el típico
father who without any bad intentions
padre que sin ninguna mala intención
because you can do it, no, you feel
porque puedes hacerlo no tú te sientes
proud of your children and you upload photos
orgulloso de tus niños y tú subes fotos
like, look at my family, I'm very
en plan Mira mi familia estoy muy
proud of my family and such. I have
orgulloso de mi familia y tal Yo tengo
two children who are Well, have you seen the
dos niños que son Bueno tú has visto al
child, I mean, the children had ads, I
niño o sea los niños tenían de anuncios
mean, the children would be Call the boy
o sea los niños serían Llamar el chico
is a character of his and I could take
es un personaje de él y yo podría [__]
making videos Well now we go to Disney
hacer vídeos Pues ahora vamos a Disney
Well now, look, let's go here, but I
Pues ahora Mira vamos aquí pero yo un
decided that the children would not appear
decidí que los niños no salían pero en
anywhere, but I don't even let my relatives,
ninguna parte pero ni a mi familiares le
but not at the level of because I'm a
dejo pero no a nivel porque yo sea
YouTuber, otherwise not even my sister can
youtuber sino ni mi hermana pueden
put it in WhatsApp photos because if
ponérselo de fotos de WhatsApp porque si
you put it in WhatsApp photos, everyone
tú lo pones de foto de WhatsApp todo el
who sees your WhatsApp photo
mundo que te vea la foto de WhatsApp
can have a photo of the child, children
puede tener una foto del niño los niños
are for the family  and that they are very handsome
son para la familia y que son muy guapo
and they look very handsome dressed as Santa Claus
y va muy guapos vestidos de Papá Noel
for the family okay because because you don't
para la familia vale porque porque tú no
know who is on the other side of the
sabes quién está al otro lado de la
screen the internet is an incredible jungle
pantalla internet es una selva increíble
and you can have
y puedes tener detrás de la pantalla a
any sick person behind the screen tell me But Javi you
cualquier enfermo dime Pero Javi se te
forget to ignore the detail that of course
olvida obviar el detalle que claro que
you are completely right but in this case
tienes toda la razón pero en este caso
Lola the girl is that she is public since
Lola la niña es que es pública desde que
no she is not necessarily public or rather
no no es pública forzosamente o sea
because she was born from fame in
porque ha nacido de lleva la fama entre
quotes or interest the cradle I
comillas o el interés la cuna yo te
am telling you what I what I would do
estoy diciendo lo que yo lo que yo haría
for example of course what I would do would be
yo por ejemplo claro lo que yo haría
I think that is an attitude that
sería yo creo que esa es una actitud que
everyone has to take but not
tienen que tomar todo el mundo pero no
just popular people but
solamente personajes populares sino
from the day they have children I mean the
desde el día que tienen hijos o sea los
children are yours When they are
niños son tuyos Ya ellos cuando tengan
14 15 years old things like that then if they
14 15 años cosas así pues ya si les
feel like it and want to go out let them go okay
apetece y quieren salir que salgan vale
but the children do not have to know
pero los niños no tienen por qué conocer
people I mean there is no reason why the whole of
la gente O sea no tiene por qué todo
Spain has to know your children
España conocer a tus hijos no los
you do not know them and that's it then you are
conoces tú y punto es que entonces estás
judging Well judging or you do or you do not
juzgando Bueno juzgando o está o no
agree that Olga Antonio
estás de acuerdo con que Olga Antonio
David Rocío Flores have been images
David Rocío flores llevan años imágenes
with the girl for years I  I don't agree
con la niña yo no estoy nada de acuerdo
with that at all. I understand that each parent can
con eso entiendo que cada padre puede
make the decision they want and I
tomar la decisión que quiera y yo te
'm giving you my opinion and maybe
estoy dando mi opinión y a lo mejor
other parents have a
otros padres tienen otra opinión
different opinion. There are YouTubers who have
diferente hay youtuber que tienen
YouTube channels dedicated to children,
canales de YouTube dedicados a los niños
so everyone can make the decisions they want.
o sea cada uno Las decisiones que quiera
Now, personally, I don't think that
Ahora yo personalmente yo no creo que
I don't think that a person who
que yo no creo que a una persona que
lives in Barcelona or the half million
viva en Barcelona o al medio millón de
subscribers that I have in Javier canijo would be
suscriptores que tengo en Javier canijo
interested in my son's face, I mean, no, they don't
le interese la cara de mi hijo o sea no
even have to know or which
no tiene ni por qué saberlo ni a qué
school they go to and when his birthday is. His
Cole van y cuándo su cumpleaños el
birthday is something that. Well, look,
cumpleaños es una cosa que Bueno mira
because for example when I had the
porque por ejemplo cuando yo tuve al
child, it's true that
niño pues sí que es verdad que todo el
everyone knows the date, how old he is, because the hell
mundo sabe la fecha los años que tiene
because they
porque [__] porque
saw Lorena pregnant and then they
vieron a Lorena embarazada y luego la
saw her the days that I was gone, those are
vieron los días que me fui esos son
inevitable things. At the end of the day, no,
cosas inevitables Al fin y al cabo no
but the less the better and everything you
pero cuanto menos mejor y todo lo que
can avoid the better. Now, it's up to
puedas evitar mejor ahora bien ya cabe
each parent to decide whether to do it,
en la decisión de cada padre si hacerlo
no, if I suddenly feel like it, just like I
no si yo de repente se me apetece igual
'm telling you this. If suddenly
que te estoy diciendo esto Si de repente
tomorrow I feel like uploading a photo of
mañana se me apetece subir una foto de
my son because I have an
mi hijo porque tengo una foto
incredibly handsome photo, I want to upload it, I upload it.
increíblemente guapo la quiero subir la
He continues, continues, continues  my
subo Él sigue sigue sigue sigue sigue mi
son can I do it what he can't do
hijo lo puedo hacer lo que no lo que no
is with another person's child or
lo puede hacer es con el hijo de otro o
that another person uploads a photo of my son okay
que otro suba una foto de mi hijo vale
but yes it is the one that Marta Marta yes yes yes yes
pero sí que es la que Marta Marta sí sí
anyway but Marta has not uploaded a
sí sí total pero Marta no ha subido una
photo with the girl obviously with her face
foto con la niña evidentemente a cara
uncovered because that's not it but it is
descubierta porque eso no pero sí que es
true that what Olgas says like
verdad que yo lo que dice olgas como
maybe it has been excessive no that maybe
quizá que ha sido excesivo no que a lo
a couple of things a little bit but
mejor un par de cosas un poco tal pero
like I think that what has
como que yo creo que lo que más le ha
bothered her the most is It's more the commercialization
molestado es Es más la comercialización
a bit like the spectacle of something of
un poco como el espectáculo de algo de
the girl's illusion at first
la ilusión de la niña yo al principio
when she posted that one on Instagram I was like
cuando puso esa de Instagram yo me quedé
yesterday I said but let's see I don't understand
así ayer dije pero a ver no lo entiendo
yes Or what else could they upload That they
sí O sea qué más será que suban Que
upload a photo of them with the girl with her
suban una foto ellos con la niña con la
face covered yes yes she uploads photos with the
cara tapada si si ella sube fotos con la
girl without without covering her you know but of course
niña sin sin taparla sabes pero claro
So I understand that what has
Entonces yo entiendo que lo que le ha
bothered her is that Marta publishes
molestado es que Marta publique
stories with the promos I imagine
historias con las promos yo me imagino
that it will be the issue of promos that
que será el tema de promos lo que le
has bothered her Yes as if it has been
habrá molestado Sí como que se haya
made into a media spectacle
hecho como un espectáculo mediático en
around  something that should be perhaps more
torno a algo que debería ser quizá más
intimate or more emotional without the need to
íntimo o más emotivo sin necesidad de
pretend I think it also goes a little
aparentar yo creo que va también un poco
more in that direction and then I think Marta I
más por ahí y luego creo que Marta que
think we can read it now Marta's thing
creo que lo podemos leer ya lo de Marta
for the first thing Marta's thing
por el primero lo de Marta
our opinion Marina let's see I understand
nuestra opinión Marina yo a ver entiendo
all the parts okay
todas las partes vale
here there is a fact that as you have
aquí hay un dato que como tú la has
mentioned it also we cannot
mencionado también no se nos puede
escape and that is that for me this is what
escapar y es que a mí esto lo que ya
was already part of it since we can be
fuera parte ya que podemos estar
debating and each one of us will have our
debatiendo y cada uno tendremos nuestra
opinion all of us who are here in the
opinión todos los que estamos aquí en el
chat about whether it seems right or wrong to
chat de si nos parece bien o mal
publish a photo or not publish it of your
publicar una foto o no publicarla de tu
son if he put a star on it and the
hijo si este le puso una estrella y la
other one doesn't or it doesn't cover his face if one
otra no lo no le tapa la cara si uno lo
does it with such but here was the part of that
hace con tal pero aquí fue la parte de
whole debate that we can
todo ese debate que podemos tener
each have our opinion With all due
nuestra opinión cada persona Con todo el
respect in the world what is
respeto del mundo lo que sí me queda
clear to me is that there is a conflict here I mean that
claro que aquí existe un conflicto O sea
here there is a moment in which they are
que aquí hay un momento en el que ellos
not I mean that maybe they have
no están O sea que a lo mejor nos han
sold us a cordiality and really they
vendido una cordialidad y realmente no
are not entirely cordial
están del todo con tanta cordialidad
because I think that if it is the first time
porque yo creo que si es la primera vez
if it is the first time and Olga being as
si es la primera vez y siendo Olga lo
prudent as she is she never wants  get into
prudente que es que nunca quiere entrar
these things and such I would have told
en estas cosas y tal le hubiera dicho a
David don't
David
do this anymore it's more sitting badly
no hagáis esto más que más sentado mal
please delete it if you want the birthday
por favor borrarlo si quieres el cumple
paid for It's that I also see it as necessary I
pagado Es que además lo veo necesario Yo
knew that there was going to be a roll with this
sabía que iba a haber un rollo con esto
since Marta about the homework on
desde que Marta lo de lo de los deberes
homework day do you remember that we
el día de los deberes te acuerdas que lo
talked about it Do you remember that you thought it
hablamos Te acuerdas que tú te pensabas
was Marta's How funny
que eran de Marta Qué risa
and I want to clarify one thing I think that today
y quiero aclarar una cosa creo que hoy
on one of the covers of the magazines
en una de las portadas de las revistas
Sorry to interrupt you Javi there has been
Perdón que te interrumpa Javi ha salido
a report about the birthday or of
como un reportaje del cumpleaños o de
Marta with Antonio David of Rocío Flores
Marta con Antonio David de Rocío flores
Manuel Vesmar and the people that report of
Manuel vesmar y la gente ese reportaje
course also has to be commented on because
claro también hay que comentarlo porque
that is also part I think that Olga is
eso también es parte yo creo que Olga
also referring to that not only
también se refiere a eso no solamente
But I'll tell you one thing that people
Pero te digo una cosa ese la gente
saying on Twitter It's clear that there are
diciendo en Twitter Como se nota que hay
people who don't know how this works
gente que no sabe cómo funciona esto la
people saying on Twitter they are already
gente diciendo en Twitter ya están
selling the girl they are already selling
vendiendo a la niña ya están vendiendo
No no that as far as I know I can't
No no eso hasta donde yo sé no puedo
put my hand in the fire for the type of
poner la mano en el fuego por el tipo de
photos etc etc etc I would swear that it is a
fotos etc etc etc juraría que es un
stolen man no then they have been
robado hombre no luego han sido
aware but that it does not
conscientes pero que no
wait Let me  explain to me what it is not I
espera Déjame explicarme lo que no es
doubt that it is an agreed upon because I know I
dudo que sea un pactado porque conozco
think I know Marta well enough
Creo que conozco lo suficiente a Marta
to know how she likes to appear
como para saber cómo le gusta ya salir
in the photo How not how And yes it is
en la foto Cómo no cómo Y sí que es
true that they are photos within what are
verdad que son unas fotos dentro de lo
such natural so I find it hard to
que tal naturales entonces me cuesta
believe that in this case as in
creer que en este caso igual que en
others I have had my doubts whether it is an agreed upon
otros he tenido mis dudas sea un pactado
exists also that it is a stolen or
existe también que sea un robado o
exists also that it is a hunted I
existe también que sea un cazado te
want to tell you that I am aware of
quiero decir que yo sean conscientes de
the presence of the cameras Wait my
la presencia de las cámaras Espera que
phone is going to turn off I enter with
se me va a apagar el móvil entro con el
mine okay here one second one second
mío vale aquí un segundo un segundo
while people
mientras que la gente
that is a very intense debate eh Let's see
eso es un debate muy intenso eh A ver
that is not the issue whether they have a conflict or
ese no es el tema si tienen conflicto o
not it's 12
no son las 12
Ah the issue Ah okay the issue is the
Ah que el tema Ah vale que el tema es la
time no no but
hora no no pero
but let's see the issue here is that I don't want
pero a ver el tema aquí es que no quiero
Marina to miss anything in this
que Marina se pierda nada en esta
conversation that they are also asking me for
conversación que me están pidiendo
the link to enter a second
además el enlace para entrar un segundo
man Javi how are you Javi do you want to send
hombre Javi qué tal Javi quieres mandar
an audio do you want to give your opinion on something good
un audio quieres opinado algo menos mal
Marina they burned me at the stake on
Marina me han quemado en la hoguera de
Twitter for saying that it is not an agreed upon stolen do
Twitter por decir que no es un robado
you also believe Javi that it is not a
tú crees también Javi que no es un
stolen is that I'm trying to find the
robado es que estoy intentando Buscar la
photo can you send me can you please send me
foto me podéis mandar me podéis mandar
what the photographs are as such to
lo que son las fotografías como tal para
put them here on the screen well I can't
ponerlas aquí en pantalla bueno no puedo
put them they are from a magazine Marina Javi
ponerlas son de una revista Marina Javi
Javi thinks the same as you Speaking clearly that that
Javi piensa igual que tú Hablando claro
is stolen do you really
de que de que eso es un robado realmente
believe that they are stolen it
creéis que son robado
is that of course it is what you say they cannot be
es que claro es lo que tú dices no se
put no they cannot you could
pueden poner no no se pueden te puede
drop or in other words from inside the magazine no you cannot take
caer o sea del interior de la revista no
them because we cannot do you
no las puedes porque no podemos
think that that is stolen Well yes let's see
crees que eso es un robado Pues sí a ver
all the newspaper archives It could make me
todo la hemeroteca Me podría hacer
think that you don't know Because things are
pensar que no sabes Porque las cosas
as they are but I think that particularly
como son pero creo que particularmente
this one yes and from there it is not that people
este sí y de ahí que no es que la gente
will say Well I have done it more than once a
dirá Bueno ya lo he hecho más veces un
second but
segundo pero
I think that in this case Yes yes or
yo creo que en este caso Sí sí o un
stolen or caught I mean caught not caught
robado o un pillado o sea un pillado no
not
un pillado no
a let's say I want to tell you that they
un vamos que te quiero decir que ellos
are aware and it is stolen and they do
son conscientes y es un robado y ellos
not realize There it is clear that yes
no se enteran Ahí está claro que sí que
yes they are aware but I do not know to
sí que son conscientes pero no sé hasta
what extent it can be an agreed I do not know what
qué punto puede ser un pactado No sé lo
those photographs would be worth today
que valdrían esas fotografías hoy en día
either do you believe it I do not know to what extent
tampoco te creas no sé hasta qué punto
I really don't know, okay, let's see,
de verdad no lo sé yo vale a ver son
in one David Manuel and
en una está saliendo David Manuel y
Rocío Flores are leaving one of the places it's
Rocío flores del de uno de los locales
still daytime, man, and then there
siendo de día todavía hombre y luego a
's a photograph of Marina that's very
Marina hay una fotografía que está muy
close, the journalists are taking the photo of her, of
cerca los periodistas haciéndole la foto
course, that's why, that's why they are
claro por eso por eso por eso que son
aware they have been able to do it, let's see, the
conscientes han podido hacer a ver las
agencies are on call and even less so at
agencias están de guardia y menos en
this time when there's no issue, so they
estas fechas que no hay tema entonces
knew about the birthday and they knew they were going to be
sabían del cumpleaños y sabían que iban
here and the agencies are there, they are
a estar aquí y las agencias están son
the agencies that sell them, then
las agencias las que les venden luego
that photograph, the magazine, it's not that
esa fotografía la revista no es que esté
the magazine Pepito is there, saying hello, good
la revista Pepito allí diga hola Buenos
morning, they are not agencies, obviously, they have only been
días no son agencias evidentemente Solo
able to sell to the magazines, in
han podido vender a las revistas de
fact I can find out tomorrow,
hecho me puedo enterar mañana
not in David's, in David's. I mean,
no en el de David en el de David O sea
in the end, I want to tell you, week two,
al final te quiero decir la semana dos
last week, no, no, it wasn't the previous one,
la semana pasada no no fue la anterior
okay. But let's see, I don't think this
vale Pero a ver esto yo no creo que esto
is a robbery, eh Javi, to Marina, stolen, not
sea un robado eh Javi a Marina robado no
stolen, no, but not an agreed-upon act. I mean, no, no,
robado no pero no un pactado O sea no no
you call the press, I'm going to be here, walking
tú llamas a la prensa voy a estar aquí
these photos, let's split them. They have
ando estas fotos vamos a medias
n't been paid,
no han cobrado
it's that Jorge, the director is very honest
es que Jorge El director es muy honesto
and I doubt he has agreed to, it's that I don't
y dudo que haya accedido a es que no lo
know.
sé No lo sé No lo sé A no ser que han
I know I don't know Unless they could have been there's also the option of Antonio David and Marta with an agency and then with that agency but of course it's a mess it's that no I think it's not worth it I want to think that not in that case in
quiero pensar que no en ese caso en
others I would tell you something else but but I don't know I don't know I don't
otros te diría otra cosa pero pero no lo
know but they send us
sé No lo sé No lo sé pero nos mandan
audios I'll put it up okay put it up for
audios lo pongo vale ponlo
a second to share people are going to
un segundo que comparte la gente va a
say tell us about Marta and
decir contadnos ya lo de Marta y lo de
Olga we'll tell you for real people
Olga lo contamos de verdad que la gente
might think it's a joke
igual se cree que es broma
[Music]
[Música]
Wait a moment yes yes yes yes of course we
Espérate un momento sí sí sí sí claro lo
'll tell it I don't know it's intense let's see I'm going to
contamos no sé es intenso a ver voy a
put the audio
poner el audio
Hello good evening Marina Javi How's
Hola buenas noches Marina Javi Qué tal
everything good evening everyone How nice it is I
todo buenas noches a todos Qué bonito es
think the photos of David's birthday we
yo creo que las fotos del cumple David
're talking I suppose I think it's just
estamos hablando Supongo Yo creo que es
stolen I think it's just
un robado sin más yo creo que es un
shot the issue of the
rodado sin más el tema de los
statements first it was Rocío's issue
comunicados primero fue el de Rocío tema
that they were lynching me and then it
de que me estaban linchando y después
was Olga's that I think was going
fue el de Olga que yo creo que iba
directly for Marta risk Why
directamente por Marta riesgo Por qué
Because Marta risk you have already commented on the
Porque Marta riesgo ya habéis comentado
homework of the  girl always
lo de los deberes de la niña siempre
like with David imitating Olga Moreno a little bit
como con David imitando un poquito a
like biting or have
Olga Moreno como como picando o lo han
I interpreted it like that then it's like
interpretado yo así entonces como que
Olga already exploded and said Look up to
Olga ya estallado y ha dicho Mira hasta
here and yes it's true that they have been very
aquí y sí que es verdad que han sido muy
clumsy but very clumsy in exposing the
torpes pero muy torpes en exponer el
girl's birthday with promotions of
cumpleaños de la niña con promociones de
places because they already know how
locales porque es que ya saben cómo es
people are and they were going to jump on her
la gente y se le iba a tirar encima
so well Twitter is hell they
entonces pues bueno Twitter un infierno
have burned me simply for
a mí me han quemado simplemente por
saying that
decir que
Marta and Antonio David have not
que Marta y Antonio David no han
exposed they have not overexposed the
expuesto no han sobre expuesto la cara
girl's face because they have covered it that the
de la niña porque la han tapado que el
video that there is
vídeo que hay
of Rocío and the girl uncovered is
de Rocío y la niña cara descubierta está
on her sister Rocío's Instagram and
en el Instagram de su hermana Rocío y
well a controversy let's go tremendous people I don't
bueno una una polémica vamos tremenda la
know people don't have I don't know they
gente no sé la gente no tiene No sé no
have no measure And if you have an opinion even a millimeter to
tiene medida Y si opinas un milímetro a
the right of what they are supposed to
la derecha de lo que se supone que
say it burns you But well I'm
tienen que decir te quema Pero bueno yo
going to give my opinion what I see and what I see what I have
voy a opinar lo que veo y lo que veo lo
said a big kiss Marina Look what it is
que he dicho un besazo Marina Mira es
Javi is absolutely right and
tiene Javi tiene toda la razón y
just while I was verbalizing
justamente mientras estaba verbalizando
you say that if you have an opinion even a millimeter to the
dices que si opinas un milímetro a la
right you  he's lynching and I'm
derecha ya te está linchando y yo
starting to think that
empiezo a pensar que realmente a la
people really don't give a damn about the
gente le da Exactamente igual el
conflict itself, they just can't stand it, I
conflicto en sí sino que no soporta o
mean, I want to tell you, let's
sea te quiero decir
see how I explain it, I'm
a ver cómo lo explico que me estoy
getting nervous with this whole thing
poniendo hasta nervioso con este tema
because it's really giving me anxiety,
porque es que me generan hasta ansiedad
gosh, since when have we been defending something for a year and
jolín desde cuándo llevamos un año y
a half and since when can
pico defendiendo algo y desde cuándo
everyone have a
ahora que cada uno tenga una opinión
different opinion on a family situation cause
diferente de una situación familiar
a schism, I mean, I think it's a
puede provocar un cisma o sea yo creo
desire, tension, desire to, you
que es ganas crispacio ganas de de me
know what I'm trying to say? So
entiendes lo que te quiero decir
I do think I think the same
Entonces yo sí que pienso pienso igual
as him. Also, I think I've seen some
que él Además creo que le he visto unos
tweets from him these days complaining like he's trying to
tweets estos días quejándose en plan de
screw around, it seems like you can't say
[__] que parece que no se puede decir
anything. What's going on, you mean, it's that they don't care about
nada Qué pasa o sea que es que además
this like a war, this
esto les vale como guerra este
internal confrontation, so to speak, is
enfrentamiento entre comillas interno
worth it like like like like to
vale como que como como como para
cover themselves in glory, the others you know
cubrirse de Gloria los otros sabes que
are like celebrating the pond so
están como celebrando la charcase tan
badly that you have to laugh Because you have to
mal que te tienes que reír Porque te
laugh the pond is shaking the
tienes que reír la charca se tambalea la
pond I don't know what's good Here I think that
charca no sé qué bueno Aquí yo creo que
at some point, I don't know if they'll even bring the
en algún A ver no sé si llegarán a la
blood to the river but what I'm clear about
sangre al río pero lo que yo tengo claro
here  that knowing Olga, besides that she
aquí de que conociendo a Olga además que
's super, she knows that she doesn't normally try to avoid
es súper sabe que no intenta evitar
these types of situations,
normalmente este tipo de situaciones
plus we're talking about the fact that
además estamos hablando de que está
Agustín is always with her like don't
Agustín siempre con ella en plan esto no
put this, put this. No, because I'm
lo pongas Esto sí lo pongas No porque
advising her, I want to
aconsejándole me quiero me quiero
refer to it, so here the first thing that
referir entonces aquí lo primero que a
seems to me is that there is a conflict here
mí me parece que aquí hay un conflicto
since there is not as much cordiality as it
ya que no hay tanta cordialidad como
seems for her to end up putting it in
parece para que llegue a poner hecho en
public. Knowing how to go straight to the
público Sabiendo como bar derecho en
public and everything that she is going to provoke
público y todo lo que va a provocar ella
with a simple story is worth it later on the
con una simple historia vale luego por
side of Marta's stories. I
el lado de las historias de Marta Yo
think that just like what
pienso que al igual que lo mismo que ha
my partner has said,
dicho mi compañero
that they have been very clumsy. I mean, they don't have
que han sido muy torpe O sea no tienen
the need to do these promotions, I
la necesidad de hacer estas promociones
mean, take the girl, you pay for the cake, you
o sea coja la niña le pagas la tarta Le
pay for her birthday, you pay for the
pagas el cumpleaños le pagas la
hamburger and you don't need to
hamburguesa y no tienes necesidad de
promote a place for her to invite you, or
promocionar sitio para que te invite o
whatever. Leave it for when you go out
sea eso Déjalo para cuando tú salgas
alone with your boyfriend, but come on, this is
sola con tu novio pero vamos esto es
David's thing too because he was right there next door. So
cosa de David también porque estaba ahí
there it seems to me that they have made a
al lado Entonces yo ahí sí me parece que
mistake on Olga's part, let's
se han equivocado por parte de Olga a
see about
ver sobre
overlapping, I also don't see the girl
sobreposición tampoco veo a la niña
because they would be covering up, I don't think that what
porque sería están tapando no yo creo
She has bothered her it is the
que lo que a ella le ha molestado es el
issue of marketing Clear clear about
tema de comercializar Claro claro sobre
exposure it refers not so much I
exposición se refiere ya no tanto yo
think to the figure itself of the girl's face
creo a la figura en sí del rostro de la
but to everything that encompasses
niña sino a todo lo que engloba
her in this case her birthday that she was
de su de este caso su cumpleaños que era
already the protagonist and it is like well that
ya la protagonista y es como bueno que
could have been a little more discreet not
podía haber sido un poco más discreto no
at the level at the social network level they could have
a nivel a nivel red social se lo podían
saved it was completely
haber ahorrado era completamente
unnecessary and there is no need to
innecesario y no tiene la necesidad de
promote anything so that they invite her to
promocionar nada para que le inviten a
the cake and the hamburger I mean they don't
la tarta y a la hamburguesa O sea no
have the need No the need
tienen la necesidad No la necesidad
need the truth is no
necesidad la verdad que ninguna
need None I also do not believe that there was
necesidad Ninguna Yo tampoco creo que
bad intention because it
haya habido mala intención porque no
cannot be if there has not been an
puede haber si no ha habido un
Olga in fact the detail of covering the
Olga de hecho el detalle de de tapar la
girl's face I think it goes that way I think they did
cara de la niña Yo creo que va por ahí
not do it with bad
yo creo que no lo han hecho con mala
intention but they said look that
intención sino que han dicho mira que
came she was having a good time not in a way Hey
vino lo estaba pasando no en plan Oye
look how good We take everything and and Hey
mira qué bien Nos llevamos todo y y Oye
on the way because they invite us No yes it
de camino porque nos inviten No sí
could be perfectly I do
podría ser perfectamente
not believe that it was with bad intention
no creo que haya ido con mala intención
to screw Olga or to provoke now of
de [__] a Olga ni de provocar ahora
course then you know what happens then also
claro luego sabes qué pasa luego también
because we have to comment on everything it has
porque tenemos que comentarlo todo ha
come out on Twitter that apparently
salido en en Twitter que al parecer
Marta would have given like  to a tweet that goes
Marta habría dado like a un tuit que va
against Olga that I don't know I haven't seen it I have
contra Olga que no lo sé no lo he visto
n't seen it I saw that
no lo he visto he visto que lo estaba
people were commenting on it if you can look at it
comentando la gente si lo pueden mirar
Oh really
Ay de verdad
how much conflict how much
cuánto conflicto cuánto
a tweet has caused her that says a picture is
le ha dado un tuit que dice una imagen
worth a thousand words if she wants
vale más que mil palabras si quiere
war she's going to have it for being a hypocrite Marta is at
guerra la va a tener por hipócrita Marta
risk she doesn't have a single photo with Lola not
riesgo no tiene ni una foto con Lola ni
a single youtuber has been able to see
un solo youtuber ha podido ver la cara
Lola's face on Marta's Instagram in order to
de Lola en Instagram de Marta para poder
make a video attacking her and she posts a
hacer un vídeo atacándola y pone una
photograph of
fotografía de
Olga and Antonio David when the children
Olga y Antonio David cuando los niños
were small posing with the children
eran pequeños posando con los niños
because they are bringing that up a lot eh
porque eso sí lo están sacando mucho eh
that they have always gone through with the
que ellos han pasado siempre con los
children it's true it's true of course
niños es que es verdad es verdad claro
for me it's not the same and it's not to
para mí no es lo mismo y no es por
defend Antonio de Villa Marta or
defender Antonio de Villa Marta ni
because everyone knows that I
porque todo el mundo sabe que yo con
have a pretty good relationship with Olga and I
tengo bastante buena relación y la
appreciate her very much But honestly they are not
aprecio mucho Pero sinceramente no son
the same times Rocío Carrasco
los mismos tiempos Rocío Carrasco no
had no impediment to the children
tenía impedimento en que los niños
going out because Carrasco herself and
salieran porque la propia Carrasco y
Fidel have also gone out walking with the
Fidel también han salido andando con los
children many times yes of course of course
niños muchas veces sí claro claro
and David being precisely the children of
y David por ser precisamente hijos de
both does not generate it  mediatically Lola
los dos no lo genera mediáticamente Lola
or rather in fact Lola has always been never
o sea de hecho Lola siempre se la nunca
spoken about as I explain to you just
se ha hablado de cómo te explico igual
as there are other younger children who yes
que hay otros niños más pequeños que sí
but in the case of Lola we all know
pero en el caso de Lola sabemos todos
Who she is but it never arises even
Quién es pero que nunca suscita incluso
sometimes when Olga shared something
alguna vez cuando Olga compartido algo
we have done the same because 20
nos hemos hecho lo mismo porque hace 20
years ago 20 years ago there was not the same
años hace 20 años no había la misma
awareness with the issue of children that there
conciencia con el tema de los niños que
is now and above all for me the
hay ahora y sobre todo para mí la
difference is that Rocío Carrasco
diferencia es que que Rocío Carrasco
was I mean at no time in
estaba de O sea no en ningún momento en
that time was it proven against
aquel tiempo se demostró en contra
Because if it had been proven
Porque si se hubiera demostrado en
against instead of filing 800 lawsuits
contra en vez de ponerle 800 demandas
by Antonio for the right to honor she would have
por Antonio por derecho al honor hubiera
filed a lawsuit like many parents
puesto una demanda como muchos padres
do for the issue of the image of the
hacen por el tema de la imagen de los
children total total total total Total I do
niños total total total total Total
n't know if Alba Carrillo did it or who
no sé si Alba Carrillo lo hizo o quien
David Bisbal
David Bisbal
on the table and And yes yes
en la tabla y Y sí sí
stop publishing because David
dejar de publicar porque David
moved they had a public move on
movida tuvieron movida pública en
Twitter that it was a fantasy for the
Twitter que fue una fantasía para los
gossip media I mean yes yes yes in
medios del corazón O sea sí sí sí sí de
fact I also remember Rosana Zanetti
hecho me acuerdo además Rosana zanetti
that Elena Tablada the ex Of course because she was
que Elena tablada la ex Claro porque era
the daughter Ela the daughter that they have like an
la hija Ela la hija que tienen como una
Elena and and  David and Bisbal and I don't know if
Elena y y David y Bisbal y y no sé si
Elena Tablada would swear that she called
Elena tablada juraría Que la llamo como
Rosana Zanet a cobra or something like that on social media
cobra o algo así a Rosana zanet en redes
and then it wasn't released, it was a
y luego no se lanzamenti fue un
Bisbal concert with a cobra. Well, it's just that it
concierto de Bisbal con una cobra Pues
was quite false with María
que fue bastante falseante con María
Teresa Campos. Look, look, paragraph, paragraph, and there
Teresa Campos mira mira inciso inciso y
are people commenting in the chat and it
hay gente comentando en el chat y me
seems to me. Honestly, the people who have the
parece De verdad la gente que opine que
opposite opinion are divine, eh, I know
opine lo contrario de divino eh sé que a
you do too, but she says, someone already says,
ti también pero ella dice ya dice
for example, these two in favor of
alguien por ejemplo estos dos a favor de
the family at risk. Hahaha I mean, it's like they
la familia riesgo Jajaja O sea es como
have to pigeonhole to
que que tienen que encasillar para
feel better and they don't realize that it
sentirse mejor y no se dan cuenta que no
's not because they don't get involved, if it seems to me
será por no mojarse si a mí me da
that it's with bad intentions because I don't
que vaya con mala intención porque no lo
believe it. I mean, don't go, don't go with
creo O sea que no vaya que no vaya con
bad intentions, the subject of going out with the
mala intención el tema de salir con la
girl doing homework or going out with the
niña haciéndolo deberes o salir con la
girl.
niña
[Music]
[Música]